customwritings.com 2009-04-13

# Privacy | We take confidentiality and privacy very seriously!

The following statement explains our policy regarding the personal information we collect about you when you visit the Customwritings.com web site (www.customwritings.com).   
This information is used to improve the content of our web pages, to customise the content and/or layout of our page. We never sell, rent or share any of the information we collect by this method (except anonymous aggregate information) with any third party.

## Information we collect as you browse our web site 

Our web server automatically collects standard information, including your IP address, browser type, operating system and access times.   
Sometimes we may use cookies to customise web page content based on your browser type, IP address or other anonymous information. 

## About Cookies

Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many web sites do this whenever a user visits their site in order to monitor visitor traffic.   
Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user. 

## Use of optional information

On certain web pages, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address or other personal information (for example, when requesting a prospectus or brochure). We will not use this information for any other purpose; it is never sold, rented or shared. We will however, use any demographic information you provide for internal market research purposes only.   
If you contact us by e-mail to request information, report a problem or provide feedback on our services we will only use the information you provide (including your e-mail address) to respond to your message. We do not share this information in any way. 

## Use of optional information

On certain web pages, you may be asked to provide your name, e-mail address or other personal information (for example, when requesting a prospectus or brochure). We will not use this information for any other purpose; it is never sold, rented or shared. We will however, use any demographic information you provide for internal market research purposes only.   
If you contact us by e-mail to request information, report a problem or provide feedback on our services we will only use the information you provide (including your e-mail address) to respond to your message. We do not share this information in any way. 

## Future developments

From time to time, we may use your information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes on this page.   
If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check this page periodically. We will only use data collected from the time of the policy change onwards for these new purposes. 

## Security 

We have appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information we have collected from you. 

## Links Disclaimer 

In order to provide visitors with certain information, this web site provides links to local, State and federal government agencies, and web sites of other organizations. A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint, accuracy, opinions, policies, products, services, or accessibility of that web site. Once you link to another web site from this web site, including one maintained by the State, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that web site, including, but not limited to, its privacy policy. 

## §537. Disclosures Prohibited

Use of information acquired from employers or employees pursuant to this article shall be for the exclusive use and information of the commissioner in the discharge of his or her duties hereunder. It shall not be open to the public nor be used in any court in any action or proceeding pending therein unless the commissioner is a party to such action or proceeding, notwithstanding any other provisions of law. Such information insofar as it is material to the making and determination of a claim for benefits shall be available to the parties affected and, at the commissioner's discretion, may be made available to the parties affected in connection with effecting placement. 

## Will Our Privacy Policy Change in the Future?

We are always improving and updating our website to further enhance your shopping experience. As a result, our policies will continue to evolve. As we implement new technology and provide new services, we will update our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to refer to this page on an ongoing basis for our most current policy and practices. 

## Access to information 

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information The customwritings.com ® holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (We charge $35 for information requests). Upon such a request we will provide you with access to all the information we maintain about you subject to the conditions of the Data Protection Act 1998. Please request this service by writing to us at the address below - [info@customwritings.com](mailto:info@customwritings.com). 

## Place free inquiry now:

If you are interested in advanced professional/master/university level writing, such as report, coursework, case study or dissertation, please send us an enquiry with the details of the paper you would like to order. Our service administrator will send you a confirmation and a payment link through email in several hours, just after querying the writers database and assigning the writer who matches your specific demands.

Otherwise, if you need custom written essay or research paper on a general topic, or college or high school level assignment, you can place an order right away without prior inquiry.

**High school**

| 

**College**

| 

**University**

| 

**Master's**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
**10 $ / page**

| 

**12 $ / page**

| 

**15 $ / page**

| 

**20 $ / page**  
  
Note: The prices in this table are given for 2-weeks orders. Please see the full price table for detailed prices.  
  
Authenticity of the writing and confidentiality of all information are guaranteed. We do not reuse ANY papers and we keep user information private.

|   
  
****
